# Javier Gutiérrez Herrera

Mexico



dukintosh@gmail.com



+523342578232



linkedin.com/in/dukindroid

## Summary

JavaScript developer of web interfaces with a background in sysadmin and tech support. I have also worked wit CMS tools like WordPress, Strapi and Payload. I can bring a web project fully from ground up installing the network, server on premises or in the cloud, to the final product guiding or evaluating the user experience.

\* Tech Stack

Frontend: React, Redux, Svelte, MaterialUI, Tailwind, ChakraUI, Bootstrap

Backend: Postgresgl, MariaDB, Mongo, PocketBase

CMS: Wordpress, Payload, Strapi

Sysadmin: Network installing, tech support, Ubuntu configuration, vps administration, cpanel Other: Payment gateways (mercadopago), Rest API's, Express, Sequelize, Wix's Velo editor

20+ years of know-how in IT Fresh and tidy JS/React/Rest API web development Rare soft skills that only an IT person out of IT can get Conversational (fairly neutral accent) english I'm all ears and sure would love to hear about you!

#### \* Contact

dukintosh@gmail.com https://dkndrd.com https://github.com/dukindroid https://twitter.com/dukintosh

# **Experience**



## Full-Stack Teaching Assistant

Henry

Sep 2022 - Present (6 months)

Bootcamp Assistant (TA) for (Nombre del bootcamp) Students.

- Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration to the study group.
- Guide students in the first steps of the course.
- Assist to solve exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Propose ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes.



#### **Lead Cashier**

Kiosko

Jan 2018 - Present (5 years 2 months)



#### The Coca-Cola Company

Oct 2008 - Nov 2022 (14 years 2 months)

### IT Assistant

**ICEP** 

Aug 2015 - Mar 2017 (1 year 8 months)

### General Administrator

**ALTOR Jewerly** 

Jun 2014 - Nov 2015 (1 year 6 months)

## DB Designer

**Brio Creativo** 

Jan 2008 - Sep 2008 (9 months)

#### **Education**

### Universidad ICEP

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Systems Networking and

**Telecommunications** 

Feb 2013 - Aug 2016

## Tecnológico de Monterrey

Bachelor's degree, Tecnología/Técnico de ingeniería eléctrica

Aug 2005 - Sep 2007

## Tecnológico de Monterrey

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

**EFSET English Certificate 80/100 (C2 Proficient)** - EF Standard English Test (EF SET)

# Full Stack Web Developer - Henry

Henry Certificate

#### **Skills**

Svelte • React.js • API Development • REST APIs • Information Technology • Customer Service • Retail • Cashiering • Figma (Software) • Content Management Systems (CMS)